[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you drink more red wine than the recommended dose, you will increase the benefits.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these seas is largest?", "correct_answer": "Mediterranean", "incorrect_answers": ["Bering", "Arabian Sea", "Gulf of Mexico"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who does Ken accidentally kill instead of the witness in the 1988 comedy movie A Fish Called Wanda?", "correct_answer": "Three dogs", "incorrect_answers": ["A whale", "Wanda", "His mother"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what city was the first permanent drama theater in Europe opened?", "correct_answer": "Malaga, Spain", "incorrect_answers": ["Vilna, Lithuania", "Rotterdam, The Netherlands", "Bucharest, Romania"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Meteoroids are small celestial bodies consisting of ice, dust and rock that form gaseous tails as they move closer to the Sun.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where did Julie first see Randy in the movie Valley Girl?", "correct_answer": "at the beach", "incorrect_answers": ["at Suzys party", "at her parents store", "at the movies"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following models of double-stranded DNA replication proved to be correct?", "correct_answer": "Semiconservative replication", "incorrect_answers": ["Semidispersive replication", "Conservative replication", "Dispersive replication"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tourette syndrome is a neurological disorder, characterized by tics -- involuntary, rapid, movements or vocalizations.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This element was discovered in 1825 by Hans Christian Oersted and is used in the production of cans for soft drink.", "correct_answer": "Al", "incorrect_answers": ["Ai", "Am", "An"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This part allows the tilting of the microscope at various angles.", "correct_answer": "Inclination joint", "incorrect_answers": ["Adjustment knob", "Stage Clip", "Arm"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What were the names of the two models killed by The Jokers Smile-X poison in the 1989 movie Batman?", "correct_answer": "Candy Walker and Amanda Keeler", "incorrect_answers": ["Amy Walden and Samantha Keller", "Cindy Wilkins and Ashley Keister", "Cathy Winters and Alicia Keaton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The popular number placement puzzle Sudoku was invented in 1979 in which country?", "correct_answer": "USA", "incorrect_answers": ["Japan", "China", "Sweden"]}]